Tierra Whack just dropped one of the
most lyrically dense rap albums of the
year, and after this breakdown, you'll
understand why.
>> What y'all [music] forgot? Cruella De
Vil, cuz I'm coming for my spot, dog.
You whack without H, so that means
[music] you a knockoff, a boulder, which
implies I got to get my rocks off,
rehearsal.
>> Tierra is coming for her spot as a top
MC like Cruella De Vil famously went
after Dalmatians, turning my spot dog
into a literal reference to a spotted
dog. She follows this with a name flip,
you whack without H, so that means you a
knockoff. Whack, of course, is her own
surname, but remove the H and you get
whack, a description of her competition
that she easily knocks off the top MC's
list. But, Tierra also uses the missing
letter to reference knockoff counterfeit
brands, which commonly misspell designer
names and poorly imitate the original,
just like her competition. Next, she
uses a rock scheme to extend the motif.
She's bolder, more confident and
courageous than her peers, but also
bolder, a humongous rock that easily
knocks off smaller rocks, hence get my
rocks off. But, this phrase also
describes an orgasm, which cleverly pays
off the scheme's coming motif. She's
been coming for her spot, and now, two
bars later, she's getting her rocks off,
meaning she came.